A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller, Vice Presidential records, Central Files, Series 3 FA378
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Invitations, 4
  - Domestic, 4.2
    - IV 1/1976/ST 45 - South Carolina (Box 207)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 46 - South Dakota (Box 207)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 47 - Tennessee (Box 207)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 48 - Texas (Box 207)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 49 - Utah (Box 207)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 50 - Vermont (Box 207)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 51 - Virginia/Cities/A-N (Box 207)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 51 - Virginia/Cities/o-Z (Box 207)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 52 - Virgin Islands (Box 207)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 53 - Washington (Box 207)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 54 - Wisconsin (Box 207)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 55 - West Virginia (Box 207)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 56 - Wyoming (Box 207)
  - Foreign, 4.3
    - IV 2 - Foreign Invitations (Box 54)
    - IV 2 - Foreign Invitations, 1976 (Box 208)
    - IV 2 - Foreign Invitations, 1977 (Box 208)
    - IV 2 - Foreign Invitations, 1977 (Box 208)
  - Other, 4.4
    - Graduation Invitations - High School and College Graduation Announcements (Box 54)
    - Graduation - High School, 1976 (Box 208)
    - Summer Internship Program (Box 208)
    - Invitations from Media (Box 208)
      From Shirley Browne.
    - Invitations for Mrs. Rockefeller from Media (Box 208)
- 1976 Presidential Campaign - Schedules and Invitations, 5
  - Schedule and Invitation Files, 1976 (Box 209)
  - Schedule and Invitation Files, 1976 (Box 210)
  - Schedule and Invitation Files, 1976 (Box 211)
- Trip Files, 6
  Contains itineraries, logistics.
  - Trip Files (Box 23)
    General note
  - TR - TRIPS (Box 192)
  - TR 1 - Trips by President (Box 192)
  - TR 2-1 through 2-5 - Trips by Vice President, 1975 January 23-February 26; Individual folder for each trip. (Box 192)
    All trips taken by the Vice President are given individual numbers and all folders provide the location of the trip or event.
  - TR 2-6 through 2-36 - Trips by Vice President, 1975 April 2-October 20; Individual folder for each trip. (Box 193)
  - TR 2-37 through 2-55 - Trips by Vice President, 1975 October 23-1976 February 12; Individual folder for each trip. (Box 194)
  - TR 2-56 through 2-85 - Trips by Vice President, 1976 February 13-June 22; Individual folder for each trip. (Box 195)
  - TR 2-86 through 2-119 - Trips by Vice President, 1976 June 24-October 9; Individual folder for each trip. (Box 196)
  - TR 2-120 through 2-141 - Trips by Vice President, 1976 October 13-December 23; Individual folder for each trip. (Box 197)
- Speeches, 7
  - SP - SPEECHES (Box 189)
  - SP - SPEECHES, 1975 September 1 (Box 189)
  - SP - SPEECHES, 1975 November 1 (Box 189)
  - SP - SPEECHES, 1976 February 1 (Box 189)
  - SP - SPEECHES, 1976 May 1 (Box 189)
  - SP - SPEECHES, 1976 June 1 (Box 190)
  - SP - SPEECHES, 1976 June 15 (Box 190)
  - SP - SPEECHES, 1976 July (Box 190)
  - SP 2-1 - Inaugural Address (Box 190)
  - SP 2-3 - Special Messages to Congress (Box 190)
  - SP 2-4 - State of the Union Message (Box 190)
  - SP 4-1 through SP 4-75 - Speeches given by the Vice President, 1974 December 19-1975 September 18; Individual folder for each speech. (Box 190)
  - SP 4-76 through SP 4-220, SP 4-222 - Speeches given by the Vice President, 1975 September 24-1976 July 4; Individual folder for each speech. (Box 191)
  - SP 4-226 through SP 4-267 - Speeched given by the Vice President, 1976 July 19-1976 December 14; Individual folder for each speech. (Box 192)
- Vice President's Recommendations for Federal Appointments, 8
  - Personnel Clearances, 1975 July (Box 57)
    Sent to Central Files by Richard Allison
    Lists of candidates for Presidential Appointments.
  - Personnel Clearances, 1975 August (Box 57)
  - Personnel Clearances, 1975 September (Box 57)
  - Personnel Clearances, 1975 October (Box 57)
  - Presidential Clearances, 1975 November (Box 57)
  - Presidential Clearances, 1975 December (Box 57)
  - Presidential Clearances, 1976 January (Box 57)
  - Presidential Appointments, 1976 February (Box 57)
  - Presidential Clearances, 1976 March (Box 57)
  - Presidential Appointments, 1976 April (Box 61)
  - Presidential Appointments, 1976 May (Box 61)
  - Presidential Appointments, 1976 June (Box 61)
  - Presidential Appointments, 1976 July (Box 61)
  - Presidential Appointments, 1976 August (Box 61)
  - Presidential Appointments, 1976 September (Box 61)
  - Presidential Appointments, 1976 October (Box 61)
  - Report: Federal Energy Research, An Analysis of Fiscal Year 1977 Program Funding Levels and Alternative Budget Paths Through Fiscal Year 1986, 1976 September 10 (Box 61)
  - Monthly Energy Review, 1976 August (Box 61)
  - Newsletter of the National Space Institute, Vol 1, no. 11, 1976 November (Box 61)
  - Peter House (Box 61)
  - Jane Orr's/Liz Haran's telephone logs, 1976 (Box 61)
- Oversized Items Sent to the Vice President, 9
  Contains albums, books, correspondence, photographs, reports, etc.
  - Caloto Ante la Historia, Book. (Box 18)
  - Our Nation and the Sea, Book. (Box 18)
  - The National Urban Coalition (Box 18)
  - Capitol Ballet Guild, Inc. (Box 18)
  - The American Reporter, Magazine (Box 18)
  - The Economist, Magazine. (Box 18)
  - PHP, Magazine. (Box 18)
  - 1975 Black History Week (Box 18)
  - Budget of the U.S. Government, Appendix, 1976; Book. (Box 18)
  - White House Public Forum on Domestic Policy, Book. (Box 18)
  - BOOK 1-21 (Box 25)
  - BOOK 22-57 (Box 26)
  - BOOK 58-90 (Box 27)
  - BOOK 91-107 (Box 28)
  - BOOK 108-139 (Box 29)
  - BOOK 140-162 (Box 30)
  - BOOK 163-164 (Box 31)
  - BOOK 165-175 (Box 32)
  - BOOK 176-186 (Box 33)
  - BOOK 187-196 (Box 34)
  - BOOK 197-222 (Box 35)
    Separated Materials
    Book 197 and Book 198 separated from the box - oversized.
  - BOOK 223-233 (Box 36)
    Book 223 separated from box - oversized.
  - BOOK 234-242 (Box 37)
  - BOOK 244-252 (Box 38)
    Book 243 destroyed prior to transfer of collection to RAC.
  - Book 253-263 (Box 55)
  - Book 264-272 (Box 56)
  - Book 273-End (Box 69)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence (Box 216)
- Mail Returned by Secret Service, 10
  - Mail Returned by Secret Service (Box 15)
    Mail returned by the Vice President regarding threats or related subjects was sent to the Secret Service for investigation. Mail from individuals the Secret Service determined to be harmless were returned to Central Files.
- Control Slips and Control Cards, 11
  - Control Slips from Daily Reports (Box 212)
  - Control Slips from Daily Reports (Box 213)
  - Control Slips from Daily Reports (Box 214)
  - Control Slips from Daily Reports (Box 215)
  - Control Cards (Box 218)
    Arranged numerically, 00100-35050
  - Control Cards (Box 219)
  - Control Cards (Box 220)
  - Control Cards (Box 221)
  - Control Cards (Box 222)
  - Control Cards (Box 223)
- Correspondence Form Manual, 12
  - Correspondence Form Manual (Box 224)
    Standard responses to typical correspondence.